Ahmad Jaffal

Full-Stack Developer

ahmadjaffal.netlify.app 🕥 AhmadFJaffal 🛅 ahmad-jaffal

PROFILE

I am an adaptable and resourceful Full-Stack Developer with experience in production-level projects. I am committed to continuous self-learning and dedicated to delivering high-quality solutions. Additionally, I excel as a team player and can bring value to any team.

EDUCATION

Beirut Arab University

2021 - 2024

B.S. in Computer Engineering

SKILLS

HTML5/ CSS / JS | React.js/ Next.js | Node.js/ Express.js | ASP.NET Core | MySQL/ MongoDB | Firebase | Git/ Github | PHP | Java

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

COG Developers *⊘*

06/2024 - present

Full-Stack Developer

- Collaborated on a project for Telegram news and channel monitoring using React.js, Express.js, and MySQL.
- Implemented live message monitoring using Server-Sent Events (SSE) and collaborated with a data scientist to process and classify data using Gemini.
- Developed an interactive real-time map using leaflet and enabled dynamic filtering and visualization of categorized news.

Connexion \mathscr{D} 01/2024 – 03/2024

Freelance Project

- Led an engineering team to develop a web application for Connexion's transportation and tourism services, with over 400 current users.
- Utilized GCP and Firebase services for backend and database management
- Integrated WHISH Money's API for payment processing and income management.
- Developed a responsive and smooth UI using React.js in addition to an admin console that facilitates management of company services.
- Integrated Google maps APIs with firebase's real-time database for live tracking of buses and recording user inputs.

Integrated Digital Systems \mathscr{D}

08/2023 - 10/2023

Full-Stack Developer Intern

- Developed a website $\mathscr O$ using HTML, CSS, jQuery, and Bootstrap that simplifies the internship application process for students and includes an administrative panel for IDS staff.
- Designed and implemented a RESTful API using PHP to handle CRUD operations with a MySQL database.

PERSONAL PROJECT

Property Pulse *⊘*

Developed a property rental service website using Next.js, enabling users to display and filter rental properties and contact owners for inquiries. Implemented Google OAuth for authentication, MongoDB for data storage, Mapbox for location displays, and Cloudinary for image storage.